Guide to the Danbury Miscellanea Collection MS 038
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Danbury Miscellanea Collection
1850-1960
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. Archives and Special Collections Library
MS 038
105
6 Linear Feet, 6 boxes and materials in map case
Comprised of maps, photographs and miscellanea collected by the University Archives since the 1980s.
Provenance
Provenance unknown. Some material likely belonged to Truman Warner. The collection is now an artificial collection of related items acquired by the WCSU Archives.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Scope and Content Note
The collections is comprised of maps, photographs (including postcards), and miscellanea collected by the University Archives since the 1980. Incuded are historic, tourist, railroad, thematic and promotional maps.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged by topic.
The files are grouped into 2 series. When fully processed the collection will be made up of a Map, Photographs/Images, and Miscellanea series.
Missing Title
Maps
Miscellanea
Photographs/Images
Local history.; Thematic maps.; Steam locomotives -- United States -- Pictorial works.; Historic maps.; Hats -- Periodicals.; Maps.; Milford (Conn.) -- Newspapers.; Danbury (Conn.) -- Pictorial works.; Connecticut -- Social life and customs.; Connecticut.; Danbury (Conn.); Danbury (Conn.); Fliers (printed matter); Danbury (Conn.) -- History.; Publications.; Danbury (Conn.) -- Flood, 1955.; Clippings.; Clippings.; Sketchbooks.; Photographs.; Miscellanea.; Chronicle (Milford, Conn.: 1892).; The American hatter.
- Maps and Plans
  - Maps
    - 5 Danbury Maps, 1856-1867; 26912 (Folder OS 1)
      General note
      Plan of Danbury, 1856: ~12" x 12"; This was originally an inset from a map by: Chace, J. "Clark's map of Fairfield County, Connecticut -- Scale 1 inch to 250 rods" -- [S.l.], 1856.
      Danbury, 1858: ~12x12"; cut from larger map
      Danbury, 1867: ~20x15"; Nearly identical to "Danbury, Westchester County" map.
      Danbury, Westchester County, ca. 1860: ~ 14x21" (Brittle)
    - Danbury, 1867; 26911 (Folder OS 2)
      ~18x36"; 5 copies: 1 encapsulated. Shows roads, railroads and important structures.
    - 4 Danbury Maps, 1880-1893; 26905 (Folder OS 3)
      Danbury Bird's Eye Map, 1880s: From card on rear of frame: "Map probably drawn about 1885. Internal Evidence. German Lutheran Church (#6) was completed 1884. City Hall (not shown) was completed in 1886." (Brittle)
      U.S. Geological Survey Map (Map 24), Danbury, Connecticut, 1889
      Hurd Atlas of CT- Hurd page 123, City of Danbury with Ward Lines, 1893
      North Part of Fairfield Co. Connecticut, 1893, published by D.H. Hurd and Co.
    - Title Survey of Lake Kenosia area in Danbury, for Fortunato and Elena D. Lottarulo, 1932; 26890 (Folder OS 4)
    - Price and Lee Maps of Danbury, 1942, 1955, 1957, 1958; 26902 (Folder OS 5)
      General
      Also contains facsimile of 1955 map.
    - Technical Planning Associates Maps, 1960; 26880 (Folder OS 6, Item 1)
    - Map and Guide of Lake Candlewood and Vicinity, 1956; 26883 (Folder OS 6, Item 2)
      Brochure published by the Kiwanis Club of Danbury. Includes information regarding Candlewood Lake, New Milford and Danbury, as well as advertisements from many local businesses.
    - Lake Candlewood Aerial Photomap, 1966; 26882 (Folder OS 6, Item 3)
      Brochure published by Beck Publishing Company; also contains many local business advertisements and a hand-drawn aerial map.
    - Facsimile plans (6) from Danbury City Hall of locations around Danbury from around 1900, 2003 (Folder OS 7)
      Includes a 1912 view of Hull block on Main Street; 1910 Tarrywile Castle area; 1910 Plans for Locust Avenue "highway"; Undated lots belonging to F.A. Hull near Housman and Hull (Now Seeley) Streets; 1913 Map of area around the Normal School; 1931 Danbury Agricultural Society, Backus Avenue.
    - Map of the boroughs of Danbury and Bethell, Fairfield County, Conn. / surveyed and published by D. McCarthy, C.E., ca. 1840; 26908 (Folder OS 8)
      1 map: col., mounted on cloth; 90 x 48 cm., on sheet 125 x 97 cm.
  - Plans
    - Candleview Ridge - A Scenic development, 1948; 26877 (Tube 1, Item 13)
    - Map prepared by Dancon Corporation, Danbury CT. RU 40 Zone., 1985; 26876 (Tube 1, Item 14)
    - Arden Hills District, 1961; 26875 (Tube 1, Item 15)
    - Richter Memorial Park Golf Course, Edward C. Ryder (Achitect), undated; 26874 (Tube 2, Item 1)
    - Map of Danbury, City of Danbury Engineering Division (2c), 1961; 26873 (Tube 2, Item 2-3)
      1 copy contains hand drawn "district" lines.
    - Powder Horn Ridge - Tentative profile - East Lake Estates (5 sheets), undated; 26872 (Tube 2, Item 4-8)
    - Powder Horn Ridge - Tentative profile of roads - East Lake Estates, undated; 26871 (Tube 2, Item 9)
- Photographs
  - Aerial image of Lake Candlewood, 1929 by Fairfield Aerial Surveys, Inc (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Protest outside prison (FCI), Danbury, Conn., 1946; 59011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Purchased via ebay, April 2015
  - 7 Danbury Postcards, 1907; 59016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Donated by Betsy McDonough, 2014
  - Danbury Postcards (Misc), 1890-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Acquired via purchase, 2015; Purchased via ebay 2017
    Includes images of Main Street, Danbury High School, Osborne Street, White Street, Maine Street, Danbury Fair, Wooster Cemetery, Buck's (Hearthstone) Castle, and view from Hearthstone Castle.
  - Bonus Crusaders, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Acquired via purchase, 2015.
  - Lee Hat Parade, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lee Hat Co., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sanford Studios Cabinet Cards, ca. 1890 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Shriner's Parade, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Purchased via ebay, Feb 2017
    Image shows Shriner's Parade going down Main Street, by what is, as of 2017, the Union Savings Bank.
  - Balmforth School Photographs, 1884-1958; 26858 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Contains portraits of grades 1-8 and High School Class (9 3" x 5" prints /J.E. Canfield, photographer, New Milford, CT) and clipping from Danbury News Times? from 1958 regarding Balmforth School's destruction.
  - City Hall and photographs of unverified locations - (frmly Misc Photo), ca. 1870-1929; 26859 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Contains an identified print of a late 19th Century Village Store/Post Office (inscribed on back as "Village Store 6 Abbott Rd." - Danbury? ca. 1870-1900).
    Image of Pershing Square ca. 1925.
    Reprint of an engraving: "Factories Georgetown, Connecticut.".
    Portrait of two women in front of a store and picture of a privy (both these photos had been originally filed together with WestConn photographs)
    4 8 x 10" color prints attributed to the News-Times depicting a food stand at the Danbury Fair (ca. 1995); an posed shot of models in front of the Sycamore Drive-in; and two shots of WestConn art faculty(?) with works.
  - Spanish-American War veterans, Danbury(?), circa 1900 (Box OS 1, Item *)
  - 1955 Flood Photograph (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Danbury Fair Aerial Photograph, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Main Street and Ives Street fire station., circa 1920 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Small box camera snapshots. Includes 5 undated, unidentified family photographs from same vendor.
- Danbury Schools and Education
  - Danbury High School's:High School Chronicle, 1906-1929; 26188 (Box 1.1, Item 1-33)
    Miscellaneous issues includes issues from:
    Feb 1906
    Dec 1911
    Feb 1912
    Jun 1912
    Oct 1912
    Dec 1912 (2 copies)
    Feb 1913 (2 copies)
    Apr 1913
    Oct 1913
    Dec 1913 (2 copies)
    Feb 1914 (2 copies)
    Apr 1914
    Jun 1914
    Jun 1915
    Feb 1916
    Apr 1916
    Jun 1916 (2 copies)
    Oct 1916
    Dec 1916
    Mar 1918 (2 copies)
    Apr 1919
    Mar 1921
    Jun 1923
    Feb 1926
    Jun 1925
    Nov 1925
    Dec 1929.
  - High School Chronicle, (Danbury High School), vol. V, no. 1-6, January 2-December 22, 1906, 26187 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. VI, no. 2-5, February 28-October 25, 1907, 26186 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. VII, no. 1, 3-5, December 20, 1907- October 30, 1908 (no.2 is missing), 26185 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. VIII, no. 1-5, December 18, 1908- October 29, 1909, 26184 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. IX, no. 1-5, December 23, 1909 October 28, 1910, 26183 (Box 3, Folder 10-12)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. X, no. 1-5, December 23, 1910- October 20, 1911, 26182 (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XI, no. 1-5, December 21, 1911- October 25, 1912, 26181 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XII, no. 1-5, December 20, 1912- October 24, 1913, 26180 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XIII, no. 1-5, December 23, 1913- October 30, 1914, 26179 (Box 3, Folder 20-22)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XIV, no. 1-5, December 23, 1914- October 29, 1915, 26178 (Box 3, Folder 23-25)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XV, no. 1-5, December 22, 1915- October 27, 1916, 26177 (Box 3, Folder 25-27)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XVI, no. 1-5, December 22, 1916- October 26, 1917, 26176 (Box 3, Folder 28-30)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XVII, no. 1-3, February 28-May 10, 1918, 26175 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XIX, no. 2, April 29, 1919, 26174 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XX, no. 2, 4, May 7-October 29, 1920 (w/ gaps), 26173 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXI, no. 1-2, 5, March 4-December 22, 1921 (no. 2-3 are missing), 26172 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXII, no. 1-5, February 24-December 21, 1922, 26171 (Box 3, Folder 35-37)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXIII, no. 1-3, 5, February 23- December 21, 1923 (no. 4 is missing), 26170 (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXIV, no. 1-2, 4, February 29-October 31, 1924 (w/ gaps), 26169 (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXV, no. 1-5, February 27-December 21, 1925, 26168 (Box 3, Folder 41-43)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXVI, no. 1-4, February 26-November 24, 1926, 26167 (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXVII, no. 4, June 8, 1928 (w/ gaps), 26166 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXVIII, no. 1, 3, November 27, 1928- May 3, 1929 (w/ gaps), 26165 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXIX, no. 1, December 6, 1929, 26164 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXX, no. 2-3, January-April, 1931, 26163 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - High School Chronicle, vol. XXXII, no. 1, May, 1934, 26162 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - The Rostrum, vol. 2, no.3; vol. VII, no. 1, undated; 26161 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - 1949 Danbury High School yearbook (Nugget), 26160 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Danbury High School, 1934-1936; 26159 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    Graduation Exercises for the Class of 1936 program, January 24, 1936 Varsity Minstrel program, March 22-23, 1934
  - Main Street School, 1931; 26158 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    The Echo, vol. 5 & 6, nos. 1-2, 1931
  - Locust Avenue School The Reporter, October 1, 1951, October 31- December 23, 1952, March December, 1953, December 23, 1954, February 14, 1957, 1951-1957; 26157 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Directory of Public Schools (Danbury, CT) 1953-54, 1970-71, 1971-72, 1972-73, 1973-1974, 1975-76, 1976-77, 1977-78, 1978-79, 1953-1979; 26156 (Box 3, Folder 55-58)
  - Announcement of Vacancy, Danbury, Connecticut Initiates Search for Superintendent of Schools, 1974; 26154 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Realia and Publications
  - Felt Campaign Hat with chin strap and band, ca. 1920; 26864 (Item 1)
    Includes box, J. Johnson and Sons, Stetson Straw Hats
  - Mallory Hats, Christmas ornament, undated; 26863 (Item 2)
  - Upper Main street Photo Print, 1970; 26862 (Item 3)
    Framed. From caption: "Looking south from railroad crossing, ca. 1870. Print made from glass negative of Col. Leonard D. Wildman and prestented to the Scott-Fanton Museum by Mrs. Francis (Tweedy) Haynes."
  - National Exchange Club - Freedom Shrine Plaque, undated; 26861 (Item 4)
    Presented by the exchange club of Danbury, Connecticut with the cooperation of Frank H. Lee Co. and Mallory Hats.
  - Mallory Woman's Hat, circa 1940-1955 (Item 5)
  - Hat City Free Press Monthly, vi number 6, Feb 2001; 55686 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Progressive newspaper active apparently from 2001-2006.
  - Kohanza Hose Co. No. 2 ribbon, 1891; 57793 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Gift from the Archivist. Purchases via eBay.
    Commemorates a reception for the Kohanza company at the Bethlehem Fire Department on Oct 28, 1891. Kohanza was no longer a volunteer company in Danbury after they had been absorbed into the City of Danbury's paid department in September of 1889.
  - The Prescription Monthly Journal, Dr. W.C. Wile editor, 1894; 58986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Acquired via purchase in 2015.
  - Borough of Danbury Bylaws with Water Act, 1882; 58984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Acquired via purchase in 2015
  - "A Yankee Humorist," bio of James Bailey, 1894; 58985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Humorists: "Danbury News Man" card, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - The Nation, 1908; 59018 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hotel Green, Mad Hatter matchbook, ca. 1950; 59017 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Map of Danbury, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Map of danbury on one side and a map of the greater Danbury area on the other side; advertisements for local businesses around the perimeter of the map on each side
  - Danbury Walking Tour Pamphlet, ca. 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Locations on tour are in downtown Danbury.
  - WCSU Sandy Hook Tribute Program, December 19, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Saint Joseph Church, 100th Anniversary Celebration, 2005.", 26145 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fowlers and Wells Phrenologists advertisement, ca. 1870 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Removed from a book.
    Purchased via eBay, 2015.
  - Shelter Rock by Edward Caswell, 1898; 57791 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    EBay purchase, Feb 2014.
    6.25 x 5", pencil on board, pen and pencil on verso.
  - Cephas B. Rogers Lighting Fixture Catalog, ca. 1925 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stevens, David B. Cyphering Book (MS 023), 1801-1812; 26865 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Biographical / Historical
    This is the ciphering book (or cyphering as it was spelled on the book) of David B. Stevens of Danbury, Connecticut. It appears that this book was begun on November 30, 1801, with the last date of entry coming on March 26, 1812.
    Ciphering books were common during the late 1700s and into the early 1800s. They were used to teach arithmetic to students, instead of printed material that is commonly used today. Student would have their own ciphering books to keep records of the lessons they were taught. A student would be given a mathematical problem to solve along with the rule for solving it. Before putting it into the ciphering book though, the student had to solve it on a separate piece of paper and have the teacher approve it before it was entered into the ciphering book. It was also quite common for the pages of a ciphering book to have patterns and designs drawn on them such as calligraphic writing. The pages of a ciphering book often began with mathematical problem, followed by the solution, and then sometimes by the rule. These books were used for many different purposes. Most often though, they were used for businesses and were used to document sales.
    It should be noted that ciphering books usually came bound in some form. This book, however, is no longer bound. The type of cover this book had is therefore unknown. Also, the pages are stained and appear to have at one time been exposed to moisture.
    David B. (Benedict) Stevens was born 16 Mar 1794 and died 23 Apr 1848 in Danbury. He was born with a twin brother, Ezra Barnum Stevens and they were the grandsons of Revolutionary war veteran, Lt. Ezra Stevens, 1724-1823 (m. Ann Barnum). He is buried at Wooster Cemetery.
    David B. Stevens married Lydia Sturges who lived on Main near patch in 1871. Their son, Erastus, was the First Selectman of Danbury in 1870.
    [100] p.: ill.; 7 x 13"
    Danbury noted on cover
    Hand sewn
  - Scrap book - "Flood 10-15-55" Clippings, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photocopies of the clippings from the Flood scrap book.
  - (Booklet) A Pictorial review of the Danbury and North Fairfield County flood of Oct. 15-16, 1955. Publisher Danbury, Conn.: Danbury Printing Co., [1955?], 26866 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    [60] p.: ill., ports.; 28 cm.
  - Danbury Images from Beer's Atlas, 1867 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    3 Danbury related clippings from Beer's Atlas Of New York And Vicinity From actual Surveys by and under the direction of F.W. Beers, assisted by Geo. E. Warner & others. Includes the Jackson Institute, Taylor and Sturdevant, Orin Benedict (Bethel), Hoyt and Sons (New Canaan) resisdences.
  - Pharmacy Envelopes and Card, ca. 1900 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    2 pharmacy cards were for products made by the Kerelis Company of Danbury. The Kerelis Company was owned by, the Danbury Mayor, Charles Kerr. Kerr purchased a building on Elmwood Place, out of which he ran the company, at auction in 1899 for $100, according to a Danbury News Times article (http://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Historic-buildings-face-wrecking-ball-247245.php)
    1 pharmacy card for "Kerr's Saline Solvent" produced by the Danbury Pharmacal Co.
  - Romance of the Rocky River, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Danbury Cultural Publications, 1923-1985; 26151 (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
    Danbury Music Centre, flyer, "1939-1940 Season," December 11, 1939
    Cultural Handbook for Danbury and Vicinity, 1985
    Danbury, Connecticut, and its Attractions, 1923
    W.F. Tomlinson Co., magazine, Nuggets, August 1930-May 1931
  - Danbury Hatting Publications, 1927-1951; 26153 (Box 3, Folder 61-65)
    Mallory Hat Co., small notebook
    Hat Makers and Hat Finishers, Locals 10 and 11,
    Danbury Connecticut, One Hundredth
    Anniversary Celebration Hat Makers, 1951
    Danbury Hat Trade Agreements, n.d.
    A Century of Hats and The Hats of the Century
    by Edward Mott Wooley, 1927
    Rediscovering Connecticut by Wayne R.
    Dickerson, 1948. (copy)
    Work, Health & Community; Danbury, Connecticut's Struggle with an Industrial Disease in Labor's Heritage, Quarterly of the George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1990.
    Clippings
  - Danbury Banking Publications, 1949-1954; 26152 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    City National Bank & Trust Company, flyer "Confidence in Danbury," (n.d.)
    Savings Bank of Danbury, brochure, "One Century, 1849-1949," 1949
    Danbury Chamber of Commerce City National Bank Building, flyer
    History, Vital Statistics and Points of Interest in Danbury, Connecticut, 1954
  - W.F. Tomlinson Co ., magazine, Nuggets, August 1930'-May 1931, 1930-1931; 26150 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Publications about Danbury, 1880-1955; 26146 (Box 3, Folder 69-70)
    Danbury Tercentenary Pageant: Pageant Participant, 1935," nametag
    60 Years in Danbury, Hamilton Press Co ., 1938. (2 copies)
    "People of the Book," program, staged by John B. Rogers Producing Company.
    A Pictorial Review of the Danbury and Northern Fairfield County Flood of Oct. 15-16, 1955.
    CT Tercentenary Celebration: Danbury-Bethel, September 15-21, 1935, 1935
    Danbury; The Story of the early Days as told to Edward A. Leary by Old Jake Purdy, 1935
    Motor Vehicle Traffic Survey, City of Danbury, 1935; 1902 Danbury Fair booklet produced by the Agricultural Commission
  - "Souvenir of Danbury Conn.", ca. 1880s; 50781 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Connecticut Military; Danbury and Our Boys in the World War by Anna Hornik. (2 copies), 1923; 26118 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Danbury Municipal Materials, 1946-1950; 26116 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    Introduction to Danbury, Connecticut, Danbury Aviation Commission, minutes, October 16, 1946-April 13, 1949
    Meserve, Albert W., "A Solution to Danbury's Traffic and Parking Problems," April 1950
  - Propaganda for Danbury KKK Rally, 1982; 26114 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Ku Klux Klan rally (Danbury, CT), 1982
  - Miscellaneous Danbury Related Publications, 1912-2000; 26113 (Box 3, Folder 75-76)
    Exchange Club, Sixth Book of Golden Deeds Awards, May 16, 1974
    Potter, Lydia V.H., Joe's Hill and the Road to Danbury," 1935
    Legends of Danbury, May 11, 1902
    Danbury News, "Just For Fun," 1912
    Danbury Evening News, January 29, 1900-2000;; 1930 real estate flier for Candlewood Lake; and 1948 flier for the Danbury Fair
  - Greater Danbury Business Digest, 1985-1995 (with gaps) (Box 4)
    Year and # of issues
    1985: 1986; 1987: 12; 1988: 11; 1989: 12; 1990: 11; 1991: 11; 1992: 12; 1993: 10; 1994: 12; 1995: 5
    Scope and Contents
    1985
    March: topics include Southworth's, Marineland, La Point, Danbury hospital, BKM, Union Savings, Medallic Art, Corn Greenhaus, Candlewood playhouse, Danbury pool, DATA HR, Workshop, Walter Southworth; July topics include Dr. Mike, Newtown Bee, Moseley, Mariano Bros., Willaim Curtis, Edward Simmonds
    August: topics include DiGrazia Winery, Allied Glass, Blue Jay Orchards, Rick LaMontagne, T.L.C. Caterers, United Painting, Luke F. Sweeney Ink, Carl Peterson; September topics include Wes DuPres, Brewster Interiors, Danbury Savings and Loan, HIllcrest Homes, Kovacs Tires, HH Stone, Betsy Pankulis, Charles Bruno
    November: topics include George Catha, Connex, Evelyn Gash, Sally Rudick, Lewis Zurlo, Josh Ruxin, BJ Dolan, Data Set Cable, Chase Industrial
    December: topics include Charles Steck, Gary Herman, Barbara Obeda, Hipotronics, Addessi, Branson, Elm's, Barol
    1986
    January: topics include David Carlin, Danbury Health & Racquet Ball Club, Intercontinental Lubricants, Associated Internists, Physicians for Women, Physicians Health Services, Dell's Auto Wrecking
    February: topics include Joann Spence, Interior-Scape, Juliard Associates, Bell Office Furniture, Walter Lauf Associates, Ron Tarsi, Ziegler Carpet, Peter Scalera Associates, John Carr, Feinsen's
    March: topics include George S. Devoe, Devoe Insurance, Danbury Mutual, Yegen Associates, Fahnestock & Co., New Milford Bank and Trust, Western Conn. Venture Capital Club, Joseph DeMaria, George Hermann, Hauser Chocolate, Con microComputer
    April: topics include Richard Jowdy, Master Built Homes, Fitzgerald & Hastings, Noce, Sirianni Mortgage, Davon Development, Remodeler's Unlimited, Victor Callirgos, Barry/Bank Street Theater, Realty Educational, Park Terrace, Danbury Ambulance
    May: topics include Tom Johnson, Lexington Gardens, Tractor Barn, Bethel Cycle Shop, Wallin Pools, John Hoffer, Caboose, EMG Printing & Litho, Fine Tools, Waste Management
    August: topics include Ancell's School of Business, Berkeley School, Bridgeport Engineering
    September: topics include Christopher Kenefick, Christopher's Restaurant, Nick's, Greater Danbury Inns, On-Premise Caterers, Chatham Oaks, Danbury Fair Mall, Fin & Claw; October topics include Jeanne Cook, Jeanne Cook Travel, Brady-Culhane Travel, Danbury Airport, Prontoaire, Ashmore Aviation, Leed Design, Corporate Angel Network, Instapack, American Sales
    November: topics include Don Lefferts, Vintage Auto, Green Tree Toyota, Levine Auto, DeMarsico, FCI, Sylvan Learning Center, Charter Leasing, Brookfield Craft, Integrity Tile; December topics include Richard Sturdevant, Sturdevant's, Creative Jewelers, Sweet Creams, Buzaid, MicroAge
    1987
    January: topics include Dr. Willian Sneider, dentistry, immediate medical care, Brookfield Chiropractic, Creative Stress management February: women in business, Karen Forcade, Essex Advertising, Karatzas, Pennington, Judy Cutwright